[
  {
    "id":1,
    "question": "What does JSON stand for?",
    "answers": ["JavaScript Oriented Notation", "JavaScript Object Notation", "Java Ordered Notation", "Java Object Notation"],
    "correct-answer": "JavaScript Object Notation"
  },
  {
    "id":2,
    "question": "What is the file extension commonly used for JSON files? ",
    "answers": [".xml",".js",".json",".html"],
    "correct-answer": ".html"
  },
  {
    "id":3,
    "question":"How do you represent data in JSON? ",
    "answers": ["Key-Value pairs","Metadata","Binary Data","Key-Object pairs"],
    "correct-answer": "Key-Value pairs"
  },
  {
    "id":4,
    "question": "Which symbol is used to enclose JSON objects?",
    "answers": ["[]","()","{}","''"],
    "correct-answer": "''"
  },
  {
    "id":5,
    "question": "Is JSON case-sensitive?",
    "answers": ["Yes","No"],
    "correct-answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "id":6,
    "question": "In JSON, keys must always be of which data type?",
    "answers": ["String", "Number", "Boolean", "Object"],
    "correct-answer": "String"
  },
  {
    "id":7,
    "question": "Which symbol is used to separate key-value pairs in JSON?",
    "answers": [":", ";", ",", "="],
    "correct-answer": ":"
  },
  {
    "id":8,
    "question": "What can JSON format be used for?",
    "answers": ["Storing data", "Sending data to the server", "Receiving data from the server", "All of the above"],
    "correct-answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "id":9,
    "question": "Can you store functions in JSON?",
    "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
    "correct-answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "id":10,
    "question": "How do you represent an array in JSON?",
    "answers": ["[1, 2, 3]", "(1, 2, 3)", "{1, 2, 3}", "1, 2, 3"],
    "correct-answer": "[1, 2, 3]"
  }
]
